bestanimations.com 2012-10-01

# Best Animations - Privacy Policy

Best Animations, and its advertisers and affiliates, are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

Effective date: 08/25/2010

Fundamentally, the privacy of web users must be protected and the most effective way to preserve that privacy is to confine their data to the site level. Burst Media as well as Burst adConductor collects no personally identifiable data, and therefore, protects user privacy while eliminating an unnecessary costly feature. Burst's TRUSTe license verifies this privacy stance.

TRUSTe

Internet user privacy and confidentiality is of the utmost importance to Burst, our web publisher members, and our advertiser clients. Our reputation and integrity are directly related to how we serve our clients and customers. Please find a description below of how Burst strives to protect the privacy of Internet users and maintain the Internet as a highly credible medium.

____________________________________________________________________________________________________

FOR THOSE WHO VIEW BURST ADS

Data Collection of User Information

All users who receive an ad served by Burst retain complete anonymity where Burst is concerned. As ads are delivered, Burst does not acquire or collect any personal information about you. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private property. Burst does, however, collect information that is specific to how you use the Internet. This non-personally identifying information can include, and is not limited to, the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring a given ad's effectiveness on behalf of Burst clients and customers.

There are instances where a user may provide specific personal information in response to an ad containing a survey, purchase agreement, or registration questionnaire. For such programs, Burst (or a third party working in conjunction with Burst and the advertiser) acquires this information on behalf of the advertiser client. The client uses this information to deliver the goods or services requested by the user. When requested, Burst may employ this information in a compiled format without identifying users specifically to provide to the advertiser client precise profiles of the types of individuals responding to the ads.

P3P 

The Platform for Privacy Preferences (P3P) provides a way for Ad Networks and web sites to publish their privacy policies in a machine-readable syntax. An Ad Network or web site will deploy P3P in order to make its privacy practices more accessible to the site's visitors. A visitor's Web browser can download the machine-readable privacy statements, and compare the contents of those statements to the user's preferences. This way, the user's browser can automatically notify the user when they visit a site whose practices match the user's preferences or warn the user if the practices and preferences don't match. Burst Media has incorporated this technology in its ad servers. Our syntax reflects our current privacy policy.

The Cookie Principle 

Burst may use cookies to improve your Web browsing experience. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer for the purpose of identifying your web browser. When you are served a Burst ad, Burst may assign in a cookie various information on ads you've seen, information on sites you've visited and activities performed to your computer browser. We do this to understand the way a user responds to the ads we deliver. For example, this information lets us keep track of how many times you view an ad we distribute. Likewise, the cookie can help make sure you do not see the same ad over and over - thus enhancing your online Web viewing experience.

Burst Media collects this information via our technology and it may be stored for up to 2 years for the purpose of: 1) analyzing campaign results, 2) ensuring that our technology is functioning properly, and 3) preventing fraud across our sites.

We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site or our member sites. We may obtain anonymous information about you – such as sites you have visited or products you have researched - from third-party sources, and combine it with data that we have collected to better target advertising that match your interests. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire. 

In an effort to respect your privacy, Burst Media gives all internet users the choice to opt-out of receiving Burst Media cookies. If you would like to opt out, please visit our Cookie Opt-out Program at [www.burstmedia.com/consumer_optout.asp](http://www.burstmedia.com/consumer_optout.asp). Alternatively, you may also choose to opt out of receiving Burst Media cookies through the Network Advertising Initiative's [Consumer Opt-Out Program](http://www.burstmedia.com/consumer_optout.asp).

Third-Party Measurement Services

Often, advertisers will employ a third-party service provider other than Burst for serving the advertisements and for tracking the performance of an ad program. These companies may employ cookie and 1x1 pixel technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their client. These companies may collect and use anonymous information about your visits to our member web sites and other web sites. The information collected can include:   

  1. Date/time of your visit 
  2. The banner ad that was shown 
  3. Unique user ID 
  4. Your IP address 
  5. The URLs of sites you visit 

This information can also be used for online preference marketing ("profiling") purposes. In these instances, Burst has no control over the information collected by the third-party, and may not be held responsible for the actions of the third-party measurement service where collected information is concerned. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

____________________________________________________________________________________________________

**FOR THOSE WHO VIEW ADS SERVED BY OUR ADCONDUCTOR PRODUCT**

The Cookie Principle

adConductor may use cookies to improve your Web browsing experience. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer for the purpose of identifying your web browser. When you are served an adConductor ad, adConductor may assign in a cookie various information on ads you've seen, information on sites you've visited and activities performed to your computer browser. We do this to understand the way a user responds to the ads we deliver. For example, this information lets us keep track of how many times you view an ad we distribute. Likewise, the cookie can help make sure you do not see the same ad over and over - thus enhancing your online Web viewing experience. 

Burst Media collects this information via our technology and it may be stored for up to 2 years for the purpose of: 1) analyzing campaign results, 2) ensuring that our technology is functioning properly, and 3) preventing fraud across our sites.

We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site or our member sites. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that use if you desire. 

____________________________________________________________________________________________________

BURST PUBLISHERS/ADCONDUCTOR CUSTOMERS:

This confirms that Burst Media is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. We also participate in the EU Safe Harbor Privacy Framework as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce. 

For Burst Publishers the privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.burstmedia.com and www.burstnet.com. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Operations at [privacy@burstmedia.com](mailto:privacy@burstmedia.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns.

For adConductor Customers this privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.adConductor.com and ads.adConductor.com. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Operations at [privacy@adConductor.com](mailto:privacy@burstmedia.com), ads.addesktop.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the web site to resolve your concerns.

Third-Party Measurement Services

Often, advertisers will employ a third-party service provider other than Burst for serving the advertisements and for tracking the performance of an ad program. These companies may employ cookie and 1x1 pixel technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their client. These companies may collect and use anonymous information about your visits to our member web sites and other web sites. The information collected can include: 

  1. Date/time of your visit 
  2. The banner ad that was shown 
  3. Unique user ID 
  4. Your IP address 
  5. The URLs of sites you visit 

This information can also be used for online preference marketing ("profiling") purposes. In these instances, Burst has no control over the information collected by the third-party, and may not be held responsible for the actions of the third-party measurement service where collected information is concerned. 

If you are a **Burst Publisher** and have questions regarding different third-party measurement services and their respective methods of information collection, please contact [privacy@burstmedia.com](mailto:privacy@burstmedia.com).

If you are an **adConductor Customer** and have questions regarding different third-party measurement services and their respective methods of information collection, please contact [privacy@adConductor.com](mailto:privacy@adConductor.com).

We do not share, sell, rent or trade PII with third-parties for promotional purposes:

Personal Information

We collect information which is provided to us such as name, email and phone number on our site in the "Contact Us" section. This information is used to establish contact with perspective publishers and is only used for that purpose.

Burst regards all personal information collected from **Burst Publisher** as completely confidential. This includes personal data provided during registration processes and financial account information. Burst does offer to advertisers any data which may facilitate the sale of advertising for a member site. This includes traffic data, click-thru rates, unique visitor information, web site geographic location, content information, and any demographic information offered by the web site member for the purpose of facilitating an advertising sale. 

Burst regards all personal information collected from its **adConductor Customers** as completely confidential. This includes personal data provided during registration processes and financial account information.

Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as Tax ID number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this [link](mailto:security@burstmedia.com).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. We use reasonable security to protect your personal information; we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at [security@burstmedia.com](mailto:security@burstmedia.com).

Disclosure

Burst openly volunteers its practices of collecting information, its targeting capabilities, and its use of cookies. If you are a **Burst Publisher** and have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please direct your correspondence to privacy@burstmedia.com.

If you are an **adConductor Customer** and have any questions pertaining to this privacy policy and its contents, please direct your correspondence to [privacy@adConductor.com](mailto:privacy@adConductor.com). 

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by logging into your user account and updating your personal information or discontinuing service at anytime. **Burst Publishers** can direct their request to [privacy@burstmedia.com](mailto:privacy@burstmedia.com) and we will change the information, as requested within 30 days. 

**adConductor Customers** can direct their request to [privacy@adConductor.com](mailto:%20privacy@adConductor.com) and we will change the information, as requested within 30 days. 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Ad servers or Web site.

Customer Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

Emails

Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, or a new account enhancement is released, which will affect the way you work with us, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. You can deactivate your account by contacting Publisher Services and requesting that your account be closed. You can reach publisher services by email: [support@burstmedia.com](mailto:support@burstmedia.com) or by phone: 800-876-4352 or 781-852-5293.

Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information that you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email with your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries to provide the services you request and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

Choice/Opt-out

We do send out regular updates of recently added campaigns to **Burst Publishers**. If you no longer wish to receive those email updates, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each update or communication, by emailing us at [support@burstmedia.com](mailto:support@burstmedia.com) or by calling us at: 800-876-4352 or 781-852-5293.

Burst does not currently share personally identifiable information with third parties. Your information is only used to provide service and support while you work with Burst Media. Should that policy change, you will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so that you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

____________________________________________________________________________________________________

Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms/Blogs

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Burst Media Corporation. Please be aware that we, Burst Media Corporation, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

Notifications of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later updates, we will never use the information you submit under this current policy in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Burst Media  
8 New England Executive Park  
Burlington, MA 01803**

**Consumer Information**

During the process of delivering an ad to you, Best Animations does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, Best Animations does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by Best Animations is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers. 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, Best Animations may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, Best Animations may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website. 

Best Animations, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. Best Animations cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time Best Animations serves you an ad. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps Best Animations target ads to you. This cookie can help Best Animations ensure that we don't serve you the same ad multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for Best Animations to deliver you an ad. 

**Best Animations** works with a third party that serves ads to this site.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  To find out more about how they manage the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to [Flycast Policy](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html) and [Sonar Policy](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm).
